《越獄》前情回顧
Previously on Prison Break
-東西在哪?   -你去死
-Where is it?   -Go to hell.
這是你自找的
You did this to yourself.
莎拉 如果你在聽的話
Sara, if you're listening,
現在只希望你能找到安全的避難所
I only hope,by now, you've found your safe haven.
我利用了你 置你於一個
I took advantage of you, put you in a place
對每個醫生來說都是噩夢的境地
that's every doctor's nightmare.
莎拉·唐克雷蒂 你瞭解嗎?
Sara Tancredi. You know her well?
如果你能把我調到隔離監獄  我對她的瞭解會更深
I'd know her a lot better if you can get my ass moved.
我會跟獄長商量看
I'll talk to the warden.
"另一次機會"和"安全避難所"
"Another chance" and "safe haven."
這都是出自一本有名的書
Those are the names of
這些詞都出自那"酗酒無名氏"的章節名
some of the chapters in the book they use an aa.
別亂來
Make no mistake about it.
我們死都要在一起
We will be a family if it kills us.
那就是你的地圖?
That's your map?
你的手腕怎麼了?
What happened to your arm?
我爸爸也是個酒鬼
My dad drinks, too.
我肚子痛
My tummy hurts.
她需要那藥 沒藥她走不了兩天
She needs that medicine. She can't go two days without it.
基斯的案子就要審判了
Kacee's going into the system now.
再加一條叛逃罪
Aiding an escaped con.
告訴她律師我會自首
Tell her lawyer I'll turn myself in.
基斯說你得趕緊跑
Kacee said you need to run.
如果你被抓了或自首了
If you get busted or turn yourself in,
迪迪就沒爹沒娘了
Dede won't have either of you.
邁克爾 我想讓這一切結束
Michael, I want for this to be over.
我們都想讓這結束
That makes two of us.
但我們得看你父親到底給你留了什麼
It's just a question of looking at whatever it is your father gave you.
就只有一個鑰匙
It's just a key.
必要的話 可以利用下總統...
If I may, sir, the president... she could be useful.
總統?
Madam president?
我想讓你回來 保羅
I want you to come home, Paul.
我們能搞定的
We can fix this,
我不要你帶這那兩兄弟到處亂來
but not with those brothers running around the country.
凱若琳...
Caroline...
把他們交給我 保羅
bring them in, Paul,
之後一切就可恢復原樣了
and everything can go back to the way it was.
保羅 克裡曼探員
Agent Kellerman.
保羅 你在哪?
Paul, where are you?
在個沒人管的地方 不記得了?
Out in the cold. Remember?
今晚我要在芝加哥發表演說
I'm speaking in Chicago tonight.
林肯
Lincoln.
莎拉
Sara.
真是有趣 當你需要我了才打電話給我
It's funny how you only call me when you need me.
也許有趣這個詞用的並不恰當
Maybe "funny" is not the right word.
這些都可解決的 保羅
All of this can go away, Paul.
是嗎?
Can it?
當然 我是美國總統
Yes.I'm the president of the united states.
回芝加哥來吧
Please just come back to Chicago
把布倫斯和斯科菲爾德交給我
and turn Burrows and Scofield in.
我答應你 我會讓一切恢復原樣
I promise you that I will make everything go back to the way it was.
我得掛了
I have to go.
回來吧 保羅
Just come back, Paul.
我需要你
I need you.
你認為我們手上握有籌碼?
You actually think we have a shot?
那得看你爸留給了你什麼
It depends on what your father gave you.
這是我找到他時從他口袋掉出來的
This fell out of his pocket when I found him.
我認不出這個標誌 你呢?
I don't recognize the insignia, do you?
不認識
No.
但是 呃...
But, uh...
莎拉 我們現在有個合夥人
Sara, we've got someone working with us now.
早上好啊 陽光燦爛的早晨
good morning, sunshine.
睡的如何?
How did you sleep?
讓我來告訴你
I'll tell you what.
我會讓孩子們出來 然後給大家弄早飯
I'll go unlock the kids and make us all breakfast.
不 我去給孩子們開門
No. I'll get the kids.
-不...    -噓 我去
-No...    -tu-tut-tut. I insist.
不
No.
我去把孩子們叫來
I'll get the kids.
塗些潤膚霜會讓瘀傷好一點
Some hand cream will make them rope burns feel better.
沒用的
It won't work.
當然有用了
'Course it will.
看這上面寫的 緩解皮膚傷痛和...
Says right here on the bottle: "Soothes skin irritations and..."
不 這個
No. This.
這沒用的 我得去工作
It won't work.I've got a job.
孩子們得上學
The kids have school.
在這段小小的適應期過後
We're all going to get back to our normal routines
一切都會回復正常的
once this little adjustment period is over.
今天有人會過來
There's someone coming over today.
誰?
Who?
一個女的 帕蒂
This woman, Patty,
歡樂購協會的人
from the welcome wagon committee.
打電話給她取消
Call her and cancel.
我沒她的電話
I don't have her number.
如果她來了 我又不去開門
And,if she shows up,and I don't answer the door,
她會發覺有點不對勁的
she's going to know something's wrong.
泰迪...
Teddy...
泰迪熊...
Teddy bear...
你得走了
you need to go.
如果她認出你的話...
If she recognizes you...
我不想你惹麻煩上身
I don't want you to get in trouble.
胡說
That's nonsense.
沒什麼麻煩
It's no trouble.
什麼麻煩都不會有
No trouble at all.
嗨 莎拉
Hi, Sara.
過去的就讓他過去吧
What's done is done.
我們目標一致啊
We all want the same thing.
你沒告訴我們你想讓她死
You didn't tell us you left her to die.
我只是嚇嚇她
I was scaring her.And I could pull her out.
不 不 你想淹死我
No. No, you left me in there to drown.
我倒想看看你能屏住呼吸多久
I wonder how long you can hold your breath.
我們來試試看
Maybe we should find out.
你們需要我 你們知道的
You need me, and you know it.
你們需要我 你們需要我 你知道的
You need me. You need me, and you know it.
為什麼? 我們為何需要他? 鑰匙在我們手上
Why? Why do we need him?We have the key.
我們會找出究竟是什麼東西
We'll find out what it's for.
我現在就可以告訴你們是什麼東西
I can tell you what that key's for right now.
這是一個私人雪茄俱樂部的鑰匙
It's to a private cigar club.
哪?
Where?
芝加哥
Chicago.
我們得快點了
We have to hurry.
我們得快點 拉瑞
We have to hurry, Larry.
我做了壞事
I did a bad thing.
天哪!我做了件很不好的事
God! I did a very bad thing.
80 30 77公路上的所有加油站
All gas stations On 80, 30, 77.
我要斯科菲爾德和布倫斯的照片貼滿每一個加油站
I want Scofield's and Burrows' pictures on each and every gas pump.
-沒油他們哪都去不             -長官?
-If they have no fuel,they can't get anywhere.  -Sir?
-什麼事?  -我們或許得把我們的注意力
-What?    -We might need to divert our attention away
從斯科菲爾德和布倫斯身上轉移開一會兒了
from Scofield and Burrows for a while.
為什麼我得那樣做
Why would I do that?
因為另外一個逃犯剛剛殺了一個公民
Because one of the other escapees just killed a civilian.
一個符合這樣描述的人
A man fitting his description was spotted
滿身血跡地從殘忍的殺人現場逃脫
running from the scene of a brutal homicide.
就發生在埃爾戈馬 威斯康辛
Happened in Algoma, Wisconsin,
從監獄裡逃出來不到四小時
less than four hours from the prison.
給麥迪遜辦公室打電話
Call the field office in Madison,
讓他們立刻找一些特工去那兒
and have them get some agents out there right away.
我馬上報告總局
Okay.I'll notify headquarters.
我沒有說總局
I didn't say headquarters.
我說 難道你不服從指揮
I said, are you not following direct orders?
我服從 長官
Oh, I am following direct orders, sir.
只不過現在不再服從你了
Just not from you anymore.
從現在開始所有事件都要聽從總部
Everything goes through headquarters from now on.
可以嗎
may I?
恩
yeah.
你聽說帕托塞克的事了
You heard about Patoshik.
就在剛剛
Just now.
很好
Good.
他跑了
He goes.
他是個精神病
Come on, the man is mentally ill.
他什麼都不知道 他並不是個威脅
He doesn't know anything, he's not a threat...
帕托塞克當過一陣子斯科菲爾德的同房囚犯
Patoshik was one of Scofield's cellmates for awhile.
斯科菲爾德把他列在逃跑計劃中
Scofield included him in the escape.
誰知道他知道些什麼
Who knows what he knows?
可斯科菲爾德和布倫斯還在逃
Scofield and Burrows are still out there.
現在不用擔心斯科菲爾德和布倫斯
Don't worry about Scofield and Burrows right now.
好 再一次
So, again...
帕托塞克
Patoshik goes.
小心點
Take care of it.
你負責這節車廂的座位?
Hi, are you in charge of seating?
有什麼我能幫您
Yeah, can I help you?
保羅克裡曼探員  特工部門
Agent Paul Kellerman, Secret Service.
我要把一個逃犯運到芝加哥
I'm transporting a fugitive to Chicago.
我需要你給我一節空的車廂
I need you to clear a car for me.
- 一個逃犯?      - 哦 是的
- A fugitive?    - Yes,that's right.
只是
Well,
我們的車廂快坐滿了
it's just that we're already near capacity...
你希望他碰到你的其他乘客?
you want him to rub elbows with your other passengers?
-不 長官    -好吧
-No, sir.   -Okay.
他以什麼罪名被通緝
What's he wanted for?
殺人
Killing people.
天哪
Good lord. Make it happen.
那確實發生了
Make it happen.
好吧 來吧 跟著我
All right, come on, follow me.
一切都會沒事的
It's gonna be all right.
如果你這麼認為的話
If you say so.
利用他幫我們得到我們需要的
We use him to get what we need,
然後就甩掉他
then we dump him.
好的
Okay.
我很抱歉你被捲到這件事裡
I'm sorry you got involved in this.
事實上你對我們的幫助
The fact that you're helping us...
意義重大
means a lot.
謝謝
Thank you.
其他的乘客不會遇到危險吧?
The other riders aren't in any danger, are they?
我的意思是 我們是不是應該發佈個公告什麼的
I mean, should I make an announcement or anything?
你希望這裡變得一片混亂?
You want pandemonium?
-不 長官   -好 不發佈公告
-No,sir.  -Okay,then no announcements,right?
只要讓所有人遠離這節車廂就行了
Just keep everybody out of this car
那就萬事大吉了
then everything is jake.
我做這事兒都幾百萬次了
I've done this a million times.
從沒發生過什麼事
Never had a problem.
好的 我照辦
Okay, will do.
好了 我們走
Let's go.
我們大概要花五個小時到芝加哥
We'll be in Chicago in about five hours.
想要休息會兒嗎?
Want to get some rest.
你還好嗎?
You okay?
恩
Yeah.
光頭
Brad.
你看上去不是很好
You don't look too good.
我幫你搞定了莎拉·唐克雷蒂的事
I helped you with Sara Tancredi,
你應該把我弄到隔離監獄去
and you were supposed to get me into AD Seg.
我試過了
I tried.
但是你的新監獄長...
But your new warden... Mm...
是一個道德上循規蹈矩的人
straight as an arrow.
但是我可以幫你弄到 一個比隔離監獄更好的地方
But I might be able to do you one better than AD Seg.
你通過俄羅斯女孩 發現了斯科菲爾德和布倫斯是嗎?
You found Scofield and Burrows through the Russian girl,right?
是的 尼卡 怎麼了
Yeah, Nika. Why?
你還通過追蹤蘇珊 霍蘭德 來追捕巴格威爾
And you tracked down Bagwell by following Susan Hollander.
是的 我用右手擤鼻涕
Yeah.And I blow my nose with my right hand
左手擦我的屁股
and I wipe my ass with my left.
怎麼了
What of it?
我有個很有權勢的後台
I've got very powerful people behind me
他希望我趕快結束這項工作
that want me to finish my job.
只要他們說一句話
They can push through the quickest habeas
法院就能以前所未見的速度
corpus proceedings the courts have ever seen.
通過人身保護權行動程序
Paperwork's sitting on the right
然後就能保釋外出
person's desk as we speak,
你違法憲法的控訴
setting forth all the constitutional violations in your prosecution.
你就等著消除得一乾二淨
It's just waiting to be rubber-stamped.
那我需要做什麼?
And what do I have to do?
你只需要找到那些逃犯
You just find those cons.
只是這次
Only, this time...
你是幫我做這個
you're gonna do it for me--
非公認的 沒有正式公文
unofficially,under the radar,no paper trail...
我需要一隻專門處理垃圾的狗去做那些髒事
I need a junkyard dog who's willing to do
將那些犯人繩之以法
the ugly things it takes to bring a con to justice.
你願意成為我的走狗 光頭?
Are you my dog, Brad?
他媽的 好吧 我同意
Damn hell, yeah, I am.
這真好吃
This is delicious.
你把它叫什麼?
What'd you call it again?
那個 我最愛的派對蛋糕
That, my dear Patty-cake,
我阿姨回巴馬時曾經叫它"流浪雞"
is what my auntie back in 'bama used to call "hobo chicken.
一份雞肉 兩份辣椒 三份真實的流浪生活
One part chicken,two parts spice,three part actual hobo.
我知道...家禽
I know, uh, uh...fowl
不是傳統的每日早中餐的一部分
isn't part of a traditional brunch, per se,
但我發現缺少肉類
but I have found a lean meat can
就像缺少開胃酒...
act as an aperitif to, uh...
會讓餐盤失去了...
awaken the pallet
食物的香味以及鬆軟可口
for more subtle flavors and textures,
就像...
such as...
天哪
mama mia!
南瓜肉桂麵包
Pumpkin cinnamon breads with
新鮮草莓和冰淇淋
fresh strawberries and cream.
哦 孩子們
Oh, boy!
你們倆怎麼遇到的
Now, how did you two meet?
在教堂
Church.
恩
en
在我出了意外之後
after my, uh...accident,
我和其他那些受切斷手術的人 一起參加志願活動
uh, I was volunteering with some other amputees.
我回到教區
My parish back home
在教會間搞聯誼活動
did an exchange program with churches
這個美好的鄉村...
all over this fine country and...
老天爺!
well...
看到一個適合我的地方
the good lord just saw fit to plop my country rump
剛巧就在我的可愛的蘇珊邊上的長凳坐了下來
right down in the pew beside my susie Q.
然後你就偷走了她的心
And you just stole her heart.
我是一個普通的獨臂強盜
I'm a regular one-armed bandit.
獨臂強盜
A one-armed bandit...
華萊士太太 泰迪叔叔給我買了輛新自行車
Mrs.Wallace, Teddy just bought me a brand-new bike.
在車庫 想去看看嗎?
It's out in the garage. Wanna go see?
好啊
Sure.
我們正聊得好好的
We have got company.
沒關係
Oh, that's okay.
這樣不行 這樣太不禮貌了  扎克 知道該怎麼做
No,it's not; it's rude. Zack knows better.
對吧
Isn't that right?
你知道該怎麼做 扎克
You do know better, Zack.
你需要有些規矩
you gotta have discipline.
如果沒有一個強硬的父親形象
Without a strong father figure,
一個年輕人會在監獄中度過餘生
a young man might just end up in prison.
看在你那麼喜歡吃藍莓派 自己不會做只能上商店去買
since you are such a fan of lame store-bought blueberry pie,
我今天親手給你做一個
I am gonna bake you a real pie...
我的名字蘭斯 我是個癮君子
hi, my name's Lance and I'm an addict.
蘭斯 你好
Hi, Lance.
嗨 莎拉
Hi, Sara.
其實我的名字不是蘭斯 我也不是癮君子
Hi,my name is not Lance,I'm not an addict.
邁克爾
hey, Michael...
你知道哪兒有水嗎?
do you know if there's any way I can get any water?
樓下的衛生間應該有吧
Yeah, I think there's a bathroom downstairs.
-我去看看     -謝了
-I'll check.  -Thanks.
那次不是個人恩怨 莎拉
It was never personal, Sara
這次鬥爭也不是
war never is.
莎拉! 莎拉!
Sara! Sara!
你還想再殺我一次 看看
you get one of those!
來!
One.
坐下來 馬上給我坐好!
Get down, right now.
發生什麼事?
What?
那三個人說他們看到
These three guys said they saw
你們快要打起來了
what looked to be a fight going on in there.
你看 我們很好 只要讓火車快點到芝加哥就行了
They didn't,all right? Just get the train to Chicago.
需要我去叫警察來嗎?
Do I need to notify the police?
你只要做好我剛才叫你做的事就行了
You need to do what I just told you to do.
你收你的票我 我來看好這群亡命之徒
You take the tickets, I'll watch the fugitive.
你們在外面想怎麼吵
You guys can just continue to do bong hits,
或者你們在那想怎麼鬧就怎麼鬧?
or whatever you do back there, okay?
管好你們自己的事情 知道了嗎?
Now would you guys mind your own business?
都聽清楚了嗎?
Everybody clear?
非常好
Great.
別再進來打攪我們了
Don't interrupt again, please.
我想我們都應該清楚
Just so we're all clear:
如果她還想殺死我的話
If she tries that again...
你要幹什麼?
you'll do what?
你先在那排座位上待著吧
Just stay on the other side of the car.
保羅 這不是個人恩怨
It wasn't personal, Paul.
這是什麼?
What're these?
我...
Oh, I'm, uh...
做了些整修
gonna do some renovations.
我剛才在釘這個石膏板 還差一個螺釘
Uh, I was just tappin' the sheetrock,lookin' for the stud.
似乎你已經找到了
Looks like you already found one.
好大一張嘴
Potty mouth!
我和那些女孩每週五都會在書吧聚會
Me and the girls get together every friday for book club.
你應該來主持這周的聚會 這樣大家都可以認識你了
You ought to host it this week and everybody can meet you.
而且我也可以再次看到你
I'll see you then!
我都等不及了
Can't wait.
不能再在這裡待了
this ain't ever gonna work here.
去收拾你們的東西 我們準備要搬家
Go pack your things, we're movin'
如果你繼續不理我的話
If you don't stop me,
我就把這些好吃的都吃掉
I'm gonna eat this whole thing by myself.
好吧 寶貝 聽我說
All right, sweetie,listen.
我和你打個商量怎麼樣
I'll make a deal with you.
還記得我們今天看到的那個旋轉木馬嗎?
Remember that merry-go-round that we saw today?
如果你不把這些東西吃了的話
You're not gonna get a chance to ride it,
你就沒有機會去玩了  快吃吧
if you don't eat something. Go ahead.
我有點不舒服
I don't feel good.
哦 寶貝
Oh, sweetie.
好了 振作點
Okay, come on.
我們走吧 好嗎?
Let's go, all right?
我抱你
I got you.
好了 稍微等下 是要甜豆嗎?
Okay, just hold on. Okay, sweet pea?
結帳
Check, please?
聽著! 所有人都不准動!
All right! Nobody move!
莎拉 在嗎?
Hey, Sara?
我想一個人待會
Not now
她怎麼樣了?
how is she?
她想一個人靜靜
Well, she wants to be alone.
我們用鑰匙拿到她父親藏的東西後
So we get what her dad locked away with that key.
接下來我們怎麼辦?
What do we do then?
我是說... 你也看到了他們是如何分析那個錄像帶
I mean... you saw what they did with the tape we made.
他們會把我們揭露出來的事情都處理好的
They're gonna bury everything we put out there.
這就是我們為什麼把他留在身邊的原因
That's why we're keeping him close to us.
他在華盛頓有很多的關係
He's got a lot of connections in washington.
如果我們去雪茄俱樂部 打開她父親的箱子
So we get to the cigar club,open her dad's box...
卻只是找到了一大堆的雪茄 怎麼辦?
what if the only thing inside's a bunch of stogies?
我覺得它值得我們去弄個明白
I think it's worth making the trip to find out.
你好?
Yes?
凱若琳
Caroline.
保羅 你在哪兒?
Paul. Where are you?
我想知道你確切的意思
I need to know exactly what you meant
你說會把事情處理好
when you said you were gonna make this right.
我要聽具體點的
I need specifics.
你在哪兒? 你周圍的是什麼聲音?
Where are you? What's that noise?
我在火車上 一會就到芝加哥了
I'm on a train. I'll be in Chicago later today.
我要知道具體點的東西
But I need to know specifics.
布倫斯和斯科菲爾德在哪?
Where are Burrows and Scofield?
他們和你在一起嗎?
Are they with you?
不用那麼擔心他們 關心關心我吧
Don't worry about them,worry about me.
保羅 在我的部門裡還有很多職位的空缺
Paul,there are still positions in my administration
無論是主管還是職員都需要人
that need to be filled--including chief of staff.
我希望你會參與進來
I want that to be you.
當我到了芝加哥 我會去見你
When I get to Chicago, we'll meet.
到時候再談
We'll talk.
把全部都拿出來
all of it.
夥計 我就帶了買三明治的錢
Man, I just brought enough to get a sandwich.
當時我就坐在那兒  真的
I was sitting right there, okay?
如果你說謊...
If you're lying...
你看我女兒生病了
look, my daughter is sick,
我不想在這裡浪費太多時間
and I don't want to spend any more minutes in here than necessary.
相信我 這是我所有的東西了
Trust me, that is all that I have.
寶貝 你有什麼東西嗎?
What do you got, sweetheart?
你有什麼東西?
What do you got?
你敢不聽話?!
You don't want to listen?!
嘿 嘿 冷靜點 夥計
Hey, hey, calm down, man.
閉嘴!
Shut up!
好吧
All right.
聽我說 你要冷靜點
Listen to me, you've got to calm down.
好吧 我幫你拿你想要的東西
All right, I can help you get everything that you want.
你也不想傷害任何人 對吧?
But you don't want to hurt anybody else, right?
來吧
Come on.
聽我說
Look, listen.
你先去前面把門鎖上好嗎?
Why don't you go ahead and lock the door,
然後把"停止營業"的牌子掛上
and turn the closed sign back,
那別人就會覺得這裡已經關門了 是吧?
so everybody thinks that this place is closed, all right?
然後讓大家都離窗戶遠點兒
And then, we can get everybody away from the window
這樣做你能放心點了嗎?
Is that cool with you?
大家都離窗戶遠點 好嗎?
Everybody's away from the window, okay?
大家快行動起來都到那邊去
Let's move everybody onto this side of the room.
去那邊 大家快
Get on this side of the room, everybody.
到那邊去 離窗戶遠點
Let's move to this side of the room from the window.
快!大家都到那邊去好嗎?
Move!Everybody,let's get on this side of the room, okay?
去那邊
This side of the room.
把我女兒也帶過去 好嗎?
Why don't you take my daughter, okay?
把她帶到那邊去
Take her on this side of the room, so that everybody...
所有人都會沒事的
everything is gonna be okay.
一切都會好的
Everything is gonna be fine.
現在你不用對任何人開槍了 是吧?
Because you're not gonna put your hand on another person, right?
對吧?
Right.
沒錯 我們做的不錯
We're all good.
是的
Yeah
我們做的很好?
all good?
我們做的很好 是吧?
We're good, right?
嘿 莎拉?
Hey, Sara?
進來吧
Come on in.
嘿
hey
我一直坐在這裡想
I've been sitting here evaluating.
我...
I, uh...
我在保釋中逃走
I jumped bail.
並被通緝
I'm on the run,
而且我剛剛還想殺死一個人
and I just tried to take a man's life.
我真沒用
I'm not using.
而這些就是我的所做所為
Which is actually quite an accomplishment.
但是在三個星期前 我還是個醫生
But three weeks ago, I was a doctor.
你可以把失去的東西都拿回來
You can get that back...all of it.
你要堅定信心
You need to believe that.
你真的那麼認為嗎?
You believe that?
你能把失去的東西都找回來嗎?
You think you can get it all back?
我選擇去相信
I choose to have faith.
如果我不相信 我就完了
Because without that, I'm nothing.
這是唯一支持我做下去的動力
It's the only thing that's keeping me going.
是啊...有兩件事讓我一直堅持到現在
I got two things keeping me going.
第一是我要找到殺害我父親的兇手
First, is that I want the people who killed my dad.
然後第二件就是...
And actually, the second...
真諷刺 也許我不應該說是誰害死了他
ironically, I probably wouldn't even say
如果我沒有失去他的話 而且...
if I hadn't lost him, but, um...
你知道...
you should know that...
呃...
um...
當我選擇這個工作的時候 人們告訴我的第一件事
the first thing they tell you when you take the job,
就是...
is, um,
不要愛上犯人
never to fall in love with an inmate.
林肯 鎖上了
Linc  It's locked.
你不可以進來
You can't be in here.
衝過去
run the roadblock.
大哥 我可不敢
Man, I can't do that.
沖!
Run it!
布拉德利·貝利克 FBI
Bradley Bellick, FBI.
布拉德利·貝利克 聯邦調查局
Brad Bellick, federal bureau of investigations.
布拉德利·貝利克 FBI
Brad Bellick, FBI.
布拉德利·貝利克 FBI特工
Special agent Brad Bellick, FBI.
你好 我是FBI的布拉德利·貝利克
Hi, there, I'm Brad Bellick with the FBI.
我是FBI的布拉德利·貝利克特工
I'm an agent with the FBI, Brad Bellick.
布拉德利·貝利克 調查局的
Brad Bellick. I'm with the bureau.
Brad Bellick. I'm with the Bureau.
我已經跟警察說過了 該說的都說了
I already talked to the cops, told them all I had to say.
我可不是那些草包警察
Yeah, well, I'm no local hayseed cop.
我是FBI
I'm federal.
你別想騙騙我就了事
And you're not going to get away with lying to me.
我沒騙人
I didn't lie to nobody.
是嗎?
Really?
他不過是個在漢考克廣場遊蕩的流浪漢
He was just some homeless guy,hangs around hancock square,
靠從高中生出乞討為生
hitting up college kids for change.
他一直在那附近
He's down there all the time.
要不是在那裡 我也不知道哪兒去找他
If he's not there, I don't know where to find him."
是不是你的口供?
That's your statement, right?
差不多
Pretty much.
哼 其實查爾斯 海威 帕托塞克
Right.See, the problem is Charles "Haywire" Patoshik
是個偏執狂 對人多的地方相當恐懼
is a paranoid,who suffers from fear of crowds,
尤其怕陌生人
who's terrified of strangers.
他要在也是在無人之境
If he's anywhere, he's in the middle of nowhere,
安分守己地當個怪胎
keeping to himself, being a weirdo.
-然後?   -如果你想來點硬的...
-And?    -And if you want to get tough...
不如我現在告你妨礙公務
how about I arrest you right now
把你抓起來如何?
for hindering a federal investigation?
誰會相信你?
Who they going to believe?
一個當差15年
An agent with 15 years on the force
並且3次由總統授勳的特工
and three presidential citations
還是一個進過少教所的小娘們?
or a piece of white trash with a juvie record?
我沒讓他這麼做 但是怕你沒注意到
I didn't ask him to do it,but in case you haven't noticed,
我對我繼父的死
I ain't exactly broken up
並不是那麼難過
over my stepdad's death.
你為什麼就不能放過帕托塞克這個傢伙呢?
Why can't you just leave this Patoshik guy alone?
他在哪裡?
Where is he?
還是你想現在就被銬起來?
Or do you want to get locked up...
有帕托塞克的線索了
I got a lead on Patoshik.
哪裡?
Where?
我這就來
I'm on my way.
拖住他
Keep him there.
讓他走單
Alone.
任何關於斯科菲爾德和布倫斯的消息
Any information on Scofield and Burrows,
馬上通知我
I want to be notified immediately.
如果能勞您大駕的話
If that works out for you.
下一站會有警察在等我們
They're gonna have cops waiting for us at the next station.
那我們得跳車
We need to jump then.
然後呢?
And do what?
躲到酒桶裡去?
Hide under a barrel?
林肯說得對
Linc's right.
好的 你放在這裡吧
Okay, you just put those in there.
真是對不起了
I'm so sorry about all this.
沒事的 寶貝
It's okay, sweet pea.
老弟 都在這裡了
Here's everything right here, man.
好了
It's good.
聽著 都到貯藏室去
All right, everyone in the storage room.
快
Now.
什麼?
What?
回去待著一直到警察來
Get back there until the cops show up.
不行不行 我不能回去
No, no, no, no, I can't go back there.
-走吧      -不行
-Come on.  -No.
聽著 你剛才一直都很冷靜
Look, you kept a cool head this whole time.
別讓我現在殺了你
Don't get yourself killed now.
你知道嗎?聽我說
You know what?Listen to me.
我被通緝了
I'm a wanted man.
要是警察來了 我就得回牢裡
If the police show up here,they'll take me back to prison,
你知道嗎?這沒什麼大不了的
and you know what?That's fine.
但是我女兒就在這裡 她病了
But my little girl right here? She's sick.
我進去了 她就剩她自己了
And she's going to be left alone.
我不能被抓走
And I can't let that happen,
你能不能放我們走?
so can you please let us go?
走吧!
Go!
這邊 咱們走吧
Come on.This way.Let's go.
聽好 所有人都到後面去
all right, everyone in the back.
動起來
Move.
-你不用走   -不!
-Not you.   -No!
你跟著我
You're coming with me.
快 動起來
Go on.Move.
你就在這裡站著好不?
Okay, I want you to stay right here, okay?
快!
Go on!
我認為你應該讓他走 老弟
Hey.I think you should let her go, man.
消失 最後的機會
take off.Last chance.
你已經拿到了錢
You've got the money.
盜竊和人身攻擊
Burglary and assault
老弟 這可是是有區別的 搶劫那不過是小兒科
Man, hey, that's change, man, that's little time.
但是你現在幹的
But this right here...
是夠讓你在監獄裡
you will be in prison
過完下半輩子的
for the rest of your life.
相信我
Believe me on that.
除非你想讓你女兒看到你死
Unless you want your daughter to see you die,
快滾
move.
嘿 我是在幫你
I'm trying to help you, man!
來吧
come here!
寶貝 站在那別動
sweetie, stay right there.
噢 不是吧
oh, no.
這是誰幹的?
who did this?
是我
I did.
怎麼樣了?
謝謝
Thank you.
海威!
Haywire!
不許動!
Don't move!
快跑 拉瑞 快點 拉瑞
Run!Larry!Run!
快點
Hurry!Hurry!
迪諾 我是艾裡克
Dino, it's Eric.
有四個乘客跳車了
We've got four jumpers.
三個男的和一個女的
Three males and a female.
快通知警方
Call it in
然後把火車停在下一站
and get us to the next station.
聽到了沒有?
Do you hear me?
快在下一站停車
Get us to the next station.
強迫衝破路障的那幾個人跳車了
The men who pushed through the roadblock are jumping off
火車正接近54里標
the train near mile marker 54,just south of the Tedford bridge.
站住! 別開槍
freeze! Don't shoot!
別開槍
Don't shoot!
轉過身來
Turn around!
我們是鐵路公司的職員
I'm an employee of the train company.
迪諾 我是艾裡克 有四個乘客跳車了
Dino, it's Eric. We've got four jumpers.
三個男的和一個女的
Three males and a female.
快通知警方 然後把火車停在下一站
Call it in and get us to the next station.
跳下去 快
Let's go. Come on.
是他們讓我們跳車然後往外跑的
They told us to jump and run
而且要我們跑的時候不要回頭 如果我們不這麼做他們就會開槍
and not to look back or they'd shoot us.
我們得找輛車
We need to find a car.
怎麼了?
yeah
我把海威逼到一個塔上去了
I got Haywire trapped.
不要採取任何行動
Don't do anything.
看住他 我很快就到
Just hold him until I get there.
沒問題 他已經孤立無援了
No problem. I got this wingnut treed.
凱若琳
Caroline.
保羅 你在哪?
Paul, where are you?
剛剛是你派的警察?
Did you send the police?
沒有 當然不是
No, of course not.
那他們怎麼知道我在火車上
How did they know I was on that train?
保羅 我一點也不知道
Paul, I have no idea.
我會轉達總統的
I'll let the president know.
我直接和總統聯繫
I contact the president directly.
布倫斯和斯科菲爾德是不是和你在一起
Are Burrows and Scofield with you?
我等著向總統匯報
I was expecting to brief the president.
你現在向我匯報就可以了
You report to me now.
保羅?
Paul?
我35歲生日 我們是在哪裡過的?
Where did we spend my 35th birthday?
什麼
What?
那家飯店
The restaurant.
你想起來在哪了嗎
Where was it?You remember.
不要這麼荒唐 我要掛了
Don't be ridiculous.I have to go.
別掛電話
Do not hang up.
我得掛了
I have to go.
抓住布倫斯和斯科菲爾德...
Just get Burrows and Scofield...
嘿
hey.
不管是誰
Whoever this is...
告訴比爾·金是他親手毀掉了...
tell bill kim that he just screwed up...
好時光
big-time.
保羅?
Paul?Paul?
這都是怎麼了
What's all this?
那瘋子爬上了穀倉
Some whacko climbs up to a grain elevator,
人們在圍觀
people want to watch.
上帝啊 你本應該處理好這事兒的
oh, god, you we supposed to keep a handle on things.
你不明白嗎?
Do you know what that means?
我給你抓到了海威 你還想要什麼?
I got you Haywire. What else do you want?
聯邦調查局 他是我的承押記人
FBI. He's my chargee.
你好啊 查爾斯
How you doing, Charles?
我不想再回監獄
I don't want to go back to prison.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
我想去荷蘭
I want to go to Holland.
我可真沒想到
That's not what i expected to hear.
但是孩子 你不可能到那裡
But you can't go there, son.
我只是...
I just...
我就是想要去... 這個地方
I just want to go...here.
看
See?
我跟你說
Yeah.I'll tell you what.
你可以不用進監獄
You don't have to go to prison.
當然你還是不可能到荷蘭的
But you can't go to Holland, either.
-哦 不不不...    -沒關係
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. -It's okay,
沒關係
it's okay, it's okay.
現在你身處絕境
Hey, you're in a tough spot.
你感到內外交困 你發現無路可走
You feel trapped, you got no options, and...
陷入這樣的地步 你自己也無能為力
caught in a situation where you have no control.
我明白你的感受
I know how you feel.
真的
I do.
痛苦不斷磨你  你唯一能做的只有逃跑
It takes its toll on you, and all you want to do is run.
但是逃向哪去呢
But run where?
我就是想要離開
I just want to go.
有一條出路的
There's a way out.
一條出路?
A way out?
對
Yeah.
從這座迷宮之中?
Of this maze?
對
Yeah.
後面是私人的煙草貯藏室
There are private humidors in the back.
每個會員的盒子上都有自己的名字
Each member's name is on their box.
有沒有警衛把守?
Any security?
只有一名招待員在那
A receptionist.That's it.
我不是通緝犯
I'm not a wanted fugitive.
給我鑰匙  我去吧
Give me the key.I'll do it.
你想不想一起去走走
Want to take a walk?
恩
Yeah.
我知道你是由於受到父母的傷害
I know you killed your parents
才殺了他們的
because they hurt you.
我也知道你昨天殺的那個人是因為
And I know you killed that guy yesterday
他傷害了薩沙 但是你這麼做...
because he was hurting Sasha, but what you did...
是錯的
was wrong.
你要明白
You know that.
我只是想離開
I just want to go.
你可以的
You can.
我現在就想離開
I want to go now.
沒關係
it's okay.
薩拉
Sara.
關於從前
Um...about before.
我也是一樣
Me, too.
恩
Yeah.